how many of you would like to be wealthy
how many of you would like to be rich
the Bible says remember we read it
earlier those that fear the Lord wealth
and riches shall be in their house how
many of you want to be wealthy how many
of you want to be rich
beloved true wealth and true richness
comes when the Spirit of God fills you
when you are no longer an empty vessel
but a net but a vessel filled with the
Spirit of God so now we're beginning to
understand beloved that in if I want to
be filled
I must pour into others did you calculi
said if I want the oil in me if I want
to be filled with the spirit then I must
focus on pouring that spirit out to
others this is very significant for us
to understand another because there's a
parable given in Matthew 25 where there
are five wise virgins and five foolish
virgins
all of them have vessels but five of
them have no what no oil how many of you
remember in the parable are in the story
of this woman that when she as long as
she had empty vessels she was pouring
out more oil continued to flow but the
moment the vessels were filled the
moment she stopped pouring the oil
stopped what flowing please catch that
point the moment she stopped pouring the
oil stopped flowing could it be that the
five foolish virgins stopped being
interested in others and were only
interested in self
how many of you want to be wise Jesus
says in Matthew 7 you got to catch this
Matthew 7 verse 24 Matthew chapter 7
verse 24 to 27 therefore whosoever
heareth these sayings of mine and what
and what everyone do with them so it's
not just about hearing it's about doing
says I will liken him on toy into a wise
man that built his house upon a rock and
the rain descended and the floods came
and the winds blew and beat upon that
house and it fell not for it was founded
upon a rock why was it founded upon a
rock because not only did they hear but
they want but they did okay now what
doesn't that say next and every one that
hears these sayings of mine and doeth
them want not shall be likened unto a
foolish man which built his house upon
the Lord sand and the rain descended and
the floods came and the winds blew and
beat upon that house and it fell and
great was the fall of it so what is the
difference between the wise and the
foolish they both hear but one does not
want do so the question is why what if
what makes the wise do when the foolish
do not know what the spirit won't come
see this notice with me Galatians
chapter I'm sorry Zechariah chapter 4
we're gonna read one through zechariah
chapter four 1 2 6 isness and the angel
talked with me came again and walked
with me as a man that is wake waked me
as a man that is waken out of his sleep
verse 2 and sent unto me what sees now
and i said i said i looked and behold a
candlestick all of gold with a bowl on
the top of it and his seven lamps Terron
and seven pipes to the lamps which are
upon the top there are verse three and
two olive trees biood one upon the right
side of the bowl the other upon the left
side of it verse 4 so I answered and
speak to the angel that talked with me
saying what are these my lord
verse 5 then the angel talked with me
and answered and said
not what these V and I said no my lord
verse 6 then he answered and said unto
me this is the word of the Lord to
Zerubbabel saying not by might nor by
power but by my want spirits say the
Lord let me let me rephrase what we just
heard here
Zechariah seizes vision a candlestick
and on two sides are these olive trees
and the olive trees are emptying that's
what is this an angel says listen this
light burns not by might nor by what
power but by my what spirit so what is
it that enables the wise to do what they
hear it's not otherwise like I will do
it and foolish alike I don't want to do
it the difference is that the rise have
oil in them and the oil in them enables
them to do while the foolish cannot do
because they have no oil in their
vessels when the oil is in you it is f
that the love of God is flowing through
you why because you are pouring yourself
into others you are giving of yourself